Junaid Shahid

10 July 1995

Address: Al Rigga, Dubai - UAE Email: Junaidshahid910@gmail.com

Visa Status: Visit Visa

Mobile: +971 50 209 6520



OVERVIEW

Hospitality professional with 1 year experience

I am a Hospitality Professional with a Graduate Diploma in Hospitality & Tourism Management. I have 1.8 years of experience at three reputable Hospitality organizations. My strengths include, Building Connections, Efficient problem solving. Enthusiasm, Commitment, Organized and Thorough I am looking for a full-time position in Hospitality industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales & Marketing Executive

FALCON ADVENTURE CLUB, ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN

May 2018 - Sep 2019

Key responsibilities included:

- Identify Key marketing opportunities and advertise/market new offers from company on all mediums especially on social media
- Carrying out effective research & intelligence into competitor products & other trends.
- To make proposals for the customized events for individual and corporate clients.

Food & Beverage Trainee

PEARL CONTINENTAL HOTELS & RESORTS, RAWALPINDI, PAKISTAN

Feb 2018 - March 2018

Key responsibilities included:

Food & Beverage Operations

- > 2 weeks of experience in Food & Beverage Operations
- Maintained knowledge of current menu items garnishes ingredients and preparation methods.
- Set tables in assigned area, or check to see that they have been set correctly and uniformly using clean pressed linen, clean unspotted silverware; clean china, clean unspotted glassware.
- Deliver exceptional service by greeting and serving customers in a timely friendly manner.

Banquet Sales & Operations

- > 6 weeks of experience in Banquet Sales & Operations
- Provided administrative and general support to both the sales and catering team.
- Communicate and collaborate all event details with a variety of departments within the hotel operation.
- Responsible for multitasking at multiple events and daily operation

Housekeeping Trainee

GRAND AMBASSADOR HOTEL, ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN

Dec 2017 - Jan 2018

Key responsibilities included:

- 4 Weeks of experience in Housekeeping
- Replenish stock of items in hotel rooms
- Monitor rooms for general repairs and upkeep
- Inspect guest rooms prior to checking in
- Accommodate requests by guests for extra towels, ice bucket, pillows and blankets

QUALIFICATIONS

Graduate Diploma in Hospitality & Tourism Management

COLLEGE OF TOURISM & HOTEL MANAGEMENT - COTHM, ISLMABAD,

PAKISTAN

2016 - 17

Coursework: Hospitality & Tourism Management, F&B Operations, H&T Marketing, Mastering Communications, Front Office Operations, Human Resources, Accounting

Intermediate in Commerce (HSSC)

SUPERIOR COLLEGE, BUREWALA, PAKISTAN

2014 - 2016

Matriculation in Science (SSC)

DIVISIONAL PUBLIC SCHOOL, BUREWALA, PAKISTAN

2011 - 2013

SKILLS

> Soft Skills

Interpersonal Skill, Communication Skill, Problem Solving

Team Management, Facilitating Skill, Presentation Skill, Confident

> Computer Skills

Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Internet

> Language Skills

English, Urdu

INTERESTS

Culinary Arts

Bartender

Barista

Event Planning

Interior Designing

REFERENCES

Will be provided on demand